this audiobook is in the public domain
you can find the text version of this
audio book at www.marxists.org
workers of the world unite
manifesto of the communist party by karl
marx and frederick engels
preamble a spectre is haunting europe
the specter of communism all the powers
of old europe have entered into a holy
alliance to exercise this spectre
popen tsar mettenik and guizot french
radicals and german police spies
where is the party in opposition that
has not been decried as communistic by
its opponents in power
where is the opposition that has not
hold back the branding reproach
of communism against the more advanced
opposition parties
as well as against its reactionary
adversaries
two things result from this fact one
communism is already acknowledged by all
european powers to be itself a power
2 it is high time that communists should
openly
in the face of the whole world publish
their views their aims
their tendencies and meet this nursery
tale of the specter of communism
with a manifesto of the party itself
to this end communists of various
nationalities have assembled in london
and sketched the following manifesto to
be published in the english
french german italian flemish and danish
languages